<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FlickrRocket</string>
    <string name="action_about_dev">About The Dev</string>
    <string name="action_about">About the App</string>
    <string name="about_app">\t\t\t\tHello, welcome to my Flickr photo viewing app. This application
        was created as part of the hiring process for Bottle Rocket in Dallas, TX. There are two ways
        to browse through the images. First,you can use your finger to swipe left or right to move
        the images. Secondly, there are two buttons on the bottom of the screen that will also
        navigate throught these photos.</string>
    <string name="about_contact_info"> Southern Methodist University\n
        Jwrowland@smu.edu\n
        817-899-8965 (cell)\n
        3140 Dyer St SMU #2378\n
        Dallas, Texas 75275\n</string>
    <string name="about_dev">\t\t\t\tI am a computer science major at Southern Methodist University
        and I have wanted to be a programmer for as long as I can remember. I love the challenge
        provided to me from a great problem to solve. Take this application for example. Before I had
        little to none experience working on android devices. Im glad to say, it has been a while
        since I have this much fun developing an applicaiton, especially getting to learn the quirks
        surrounding Android OS. Luckly I had a vast background in java programming which helped me
        greatly in this project. Anyways, back to me. Im currently a sophtmore planning on graduating
        during the spring of 2019, but already egear to join the work force over the summer.
        Especially if its new and challenging. I appreciate the tiem you have taken to both read
        about me and partake in my application. Hopefully as I learn more, I can improve the visual
        quality of it, but I can tell you the inner workings are my favorite part. Feel free to
        contact me at any time.
        \n
        \n
        Thank you all.</string>
</resources>
